Guide to the Pittsburgh Regional Library Center Records, 1967-1985 AIS.1990.12
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Reciprocal borrowing agreement, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Reciprocal borrowing agreement, 1976-1977 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Reciprocal borrowing agreement, 1977-1978 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Reciprocal borrowing committee, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Reciprocal borrowing committee, 1979-1980 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Reciprocal borrowing committee, 1980-1981 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Reciprocal borrowing committee, 1981-1982 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Reciprocal borrowing committee, 1982-1983 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Reciprocal borrowing committee, 1983-1984 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Regional Meeting (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Regional Resources Directory, 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Regional Resources Directory, 1979-1980 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Regional Resources Directory, 1980-1981 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Regional Resources Directory, 1981-1982 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Regional Resources Directory, 1982-1983 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Regional Resources Directory, 1983-1984 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Research and Development Committee, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Research and Development Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- Research and Development Committee, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- Research and Development Committee, 1981-1982 (Box 8, Folder 21)
- Research and Development Committee, 1982-1983 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- Research and Development Committee, 1983-1984 (Box 8, Folder 23)
- Research and Development Committee, Resource Sharing Committee, 1982-1984 (Box 8, Folder 24)
- Search Committee, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 25)
- Serials Data Base to OCLC, 1974-1975 (Box 8, Folder 26)
- Speeches about PRLC, 1967-1973 (Box 8, Folder 27)
- Sharing of non-book A/U resources, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 28)
- Short and long term planning, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 29)
- Technical Process- Contracts, correspondence (Box 8, Folder 30)
- Technical Process- Statistics, prod. info. (Box 8, Folder 31)
- Undergraduate Borrowing, 1974-1975 (Box 8, Folder 32)
- Undergraduate Borrowing, Forms, 1975-1977 (Box 8, Folder 33)
- Undergraduate Borrowing, Notices, 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 34)
- Undergraduate Borrowing, Forms, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 35)
- Undergraduate Borrowing, Notices, 1976-1977 (Box 8, Folder 36)
- Undergraduate Borrowing, Notices, 1977-1978 (Box 8, Folder 37)
- Undergraduate Borrowing, Notices, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 38)
- Undergraduate Borrowing, Signatures, 1976-1977 (Box 8, Folder 39)
- Undergraduate Borrowing, Signatures, 1977-1978 (Box 8, Folder 40)
- Undergraduate Borrowing, Signatures, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 41)
- Union Lib catalogue: grant/searching ILL, July 1976-June 1977 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Union list of periodicals, 1974-1975 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Union list of periodicals, 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Union list of periodicals, 1976-1977 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Union list of periodicals, 1977-1978 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Union list of periodicals committee, 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Union list of periodicals committee, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Union list of periodicals committee, 1980-1981 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Union list of periodicals committee, 1981-1982 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Union list of periodicals committee, 1982-1983 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Union list of periodicals committee, 1983-1984 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Union list workshop on serials, November 1976 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Conversion (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Core merge (Box 9, Folder 14)
- [Empty file folder] (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Institutions list - core one (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Equipment (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Manual (Box 9, Folder 18)
- AULS - adv. comm. (Box 9, Folder 19)
- PRLC Union list, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- PRLC Union list, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 21)
- PRLC Union list, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 22)
- State contract, Year 1 (Box 9, Folder 23)
- State contract, Year 2 (Box 9, Folder 24)
- State contract, Quarterly reports--Year 2 (Box 9, Folder 25)
- State contract, Monthly statistics--Year 2 (Box 9, Folder 26)
- State contract, Year 3 (Box 9, Folder 27)
- State contract, Monthly reports--Year 3 (Box 9, Folder 28)
- State contract, Quarterly reports--Year 3 (Box 9, Folder 29)
- State contract, Year 4 (Box 9, Folder 30)
- State contract, Monthly reports--Year 4 (Box 9, Folder 31)
- State contract, Quarterly reports--Year 4 (Box 9, Folder 32)
- State contract, Year 5 (Box 9, Folder 33)
- State contract, Monthly statistics--Year 5 (Box 9, Folder 34)
- State contract, Quarterly reports--Year 5 (Box 9, Folder 35)
- State contract, Pauls - audit, 1983-84 (Box 9, Folder 36)
- User Education Committee, 1984-1985 (Box 9, Folder 37)
- User Education Committee, 1985-1986 (Box 9, Folder 38)
- User Services - PRLC photocopy exchange program, General file (Box 9, Folder 39)
- User Services - PRLC photocopy exchange program, Statistics (Box 9, Folder 40)
- Warehouse Committee, 1982-83 (Box 9, Folder 41)
- Ways Means, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 42)
- Ways Means, 1974-1975 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Ways Means, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Ways Means, 1976-1977 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Ways Means, 1968-1971 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Ways Means, 1971-1972 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Ways Means, Open House Program (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Western Pennsylvania, By laws, 1974-1975 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Western Pennsylvania, Resources, 1974-1975 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Western Pennsylvania, Resources, 1976-1977 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Western Pennsylvania, Directory, 1977-1978 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Western Pennsylvania, Committee (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Workshops- Clarion, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Workshops- Erie, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Workshops- Microcomputers, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Workshops- New Castle, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Workshops- Warren, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Workshops- On resources sharing in Pennsylvania libraries, in Hershey, Pa., Feb. 21-23, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Booklets (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - A. Altoona Automation Plan: A Final Report, 1983; 2 copies
  - B. Preliminary Report Altoona Feasibility Study, Feb. 83
  - C. Budget Proposal PRLC, 1977-1978
  - D. Communications and Access System: a PRLC/Palinet Proposal
  - E. Cooperation in the White Pine Region: a Proposal, 2 copies
  - F. General correspondence, 1979-1980
  - G. Guide to the Electronic Mail System, July, 1984
  - H. LSCA Project No. 79-26
  - I. Organization Library "COOP" Group Pgh. Cooperative Council of Academic Libraries Meetings, 1965-1966
  - J. Major microform holdings in eight PRLC Libraries, revised edition, June 1973
  - K. Mercyhurst College Space Utilization Study, March 1983; 12 copies
  - L. Minutes and reports of PRLC Committees, 1975
  - M. New Literacy Council follow through, Aug. 30, 1984
  - N. Oglebay Institute on Quality Control, Nov. 12-14, 1982
  - O. Proposal for production of a computer output microfiche (COM) Catalog for the State Library of Pennsylvania
  - P. Requests to PRLC, 1973-1975
  - Q. South Dakota Lib. Automation Plan First Report, 1983; 2 copies
  - R. Webnet Project evaluation, phase one: Current system operations, 1981; 12 copies
  - S. Webnet Project Evaluation, phase two: Fully Integrated System, 1981